[scary music]
[恐怖音乐]
*
- Listen up, crew.
I have an announcement!
- 听着，船员们。
我有一个公告！
Bikini Bottom's
new sports stadium
比基尼泳裤
新体育场
will officially be named
after this restaurant!
将被正式命名
在这家餐厅之后！
- The Krusty Krab Stadium!
Wow!
- 蟹堡王体育场！
哇！
- Soon I'll have all
the concessions in the stadium.
- 很快我就会拥有一切
体育场内的优惠。
Paying for the naming rights
will make me millions!
支付冠名权费用
将使我赚到数百万！
- Opening day is today!
Tailgate party!
- 今天是开幕日！
车尾派对！
- Not for you.
- 不适合你。
Your tails
have to stay here
你的尾巴
必须留在这里
and make me back
some of that money I spent.
让我回来
我花掉了其中一些钱。
- Hooray for Mr. Krabs!
- 蟹老板万岁！
- While I'm gone,
Squidward mans the helm.
- 当我不在的时候，
章鱼哥掌舵。
- [snoring]
- [打鼾]
- Psst.
Hey, Squidward.
- 嘘。
嘿，章鱼哥。
- Oh, Teddy, you're
my favorite snuggle buddy.
- 哦，泰迪，你是
我最喜欢的依偎伙伴。
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- Okay, boss, give me
a job to do, please.
- 好的，老板，给我
有工作要做，拜托。
- Well, why don't you clean
the, uh--
- 好吧，你为什么不干净呢？
的，呃——
Well, you could always
clean the, uh--
好吧，你总是可以
清理，呃——
Why don't you clean
your own--
你为什么不干净
你自己的——
Oh.
哦。
All right, all right, um...
好吧好吧，嗯……
clean everything
one more time.
清洁一切
再过一次。
- On it!
- 就它了！
- [snores]
- [打鼾]
- Done.
More, please.
- 完毕。
请更多。
- Two more times.
- 再过两次。
- Done, done.
- 完成了，完成了。
- Ah, but did you clean down
to the subatomic particles?
- 啊，但是你清理干净了吗？
到亚原子粒子？
- [grunts]
I knew I missed something.
- [咕哝]
我知道我错过了一些东西。
- Done.
Even the theoretical particles
- 完毕。
即使是理论粒子
are clean, theoretically.
理论上是干净的。
[laughs]
- Um, I don't know.
[笑]
- 嗯，我不知道。
Why don't you just--
I don't know--
你为什么不只是——
我不知道——
see how many things
you can flush down the toilet?
看看有多少东西
你可以冲马桶吗？
- Um, are you sure
about that, boss?
- 嗯，你确定吗
老板，关于这个？
- Are you questioning
my orders?
- 你在质疑吗
我的命令？
- I hear and obey,
my liege.
- 我听到并服从，
我的君主。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- [snores]
- [打鼾]
[screams]
What have I done?
[尖叫声]
我做了什么？
- How am I doing, boss?
- 我怎么样，老板？
- This is a completely
irresponsible thing to do!
- 这完全是一个
做不负责任的事！
But I must admit,
it looks amazing.
但我必须承认，
看起来棒极了。
- How about this?
- 这个怎么样？
- Here, try this!
- 来，试试这个！
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- Here you go!
- 干得好！
[both panting]
[两人都气喘吁吁]
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
- This'll go down good.
[grunts]
- 这会进展顺利。
[咕哝]
Oops.
哎呀。
- Huh?
- 啊？
[grunting and laughing]
[咕哝和大笑]
- That was funny. It almost
looked like Mr. Krabs' safe--
- 这很有趣。差不多了
看起来就像蟹老板的保险箱——
you know, the one
你知道，那个
with the secret
Krabby Patty formula inside?
与秘密
里面有蟹黄饼配方吗？
- [laughs]
What's really funny is that
- [笑]
真正有趣的是
it was Mr. Krabs' safe,
the one with the--
这是蟹老板的保险箱，
那个有——
both: Secret Krabby Patty
formula inside!
两者：秘密蟹黄帕蒂
里面有公式！
- How could you?
- 你怎么可以？
- You ordered me to!
- 你命令我这么做的！
- I didn't say the safe!
- 我没说保险箱！
- You didn't say
not the safe.
-你没说
不是保险箱。
- Well, I order you
to go get it!
- 好吧，我命令你
去拿吧！
- One second.
- 一秒钟。
Employees must wash hands
before leaving.
员工必须洗手
离开之前。
[adventurous music]
[冒险音乐]
*
- What have I done?
- 我做了什么？
I flushed SpongeBob
down the toilet.
我把海绵宝宝冲红了
下厕所。
Why, that's despicable,
even for me.
为什么，这太卑鄙了
即使对我来说也是如此。
[all murmuring]
- All right,
[大家窃窃私语]
- 好吧，
as soon as I get the fry cook
out of the toilet,
我一拿到炒菜厨师
从厕所出来，
you can all have
your Krabby Patties.
你们都可以拥有
你的蟹黄饼。
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
Yuck.
恶心。
It's so unsanitary.
太不卫生了
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
我不敢相信
我正在做这个。
[marching band music]
[行进乐队音乐]
- Ow!
- Krabs, you old bag of shells.
- 噢！
- 螃蟹，你这个老贝壳袋。
You're not gonna regret
paying that money
你不会后悔的
付那笔钱
to have your name
on this stadium I built for you.
有你的名字
在我为你建造的这个体育场上。
- I sure hope
you're right.
- 我当然希望
你是对的。
- Oh!
- Oh, Krabs, I'd like you
- 哦！
- 哦，蟹蟹，我想要你
to meet Charlton Hawkfish,
the famous sewer architect.
去见查尔顿鹰鱼，
著名的下水道建筑师。
- I designed every pipe,
gasket, and cesspit
- 我设计了每根管道，
垫圈和污水坑
beneath this stadium.
在这个体育场的下面。
- [chuckles]
Eh, hi.
- [轻笑]
呃，嗨。
- That was weird.
I had to flush the toilet twice.
- 这很奇怪。
我不得不冲厕所两次。
- And they call this is place
a modern marvel.
- 他们称这就是地方
现代奇迹。
- Crupski, you told me
you wouldn't cut corners
- 克鲁普斯基，你告诉我的
你不会偷工减料
on my plans!
按照我的计划！
What's this?
Ah!
这是什么？
啊!
You've added a reducer
into a 5-foot main line!
您添加了一个减速器
进入5英尺的主线！
- Your point being?
- 你的意思是？
- That pipe's too small!
It'll never hold.
- 那个管子太小了！
它永远不会持有。
- Relax, Charlton.
- 放松，查尔顿。
Building it cheap
saved a lot of money.
建造成本低廉
节省了很多钱。
- Ooh!
I like that.
- 哦！
我喜欢这样。
- And what's this?
- 这是什么？
The pipe is made
out of cardboard?
管道已制成
用纸板？
- Eh, corrugated cardboard.
- 呃，瓦楞纸板。
- Ah, relax.
- 啊，放松点。
That's what my grandma's
dentures are made of.
这就是我奶奶的
假牙是由.
- Aah!
- 啊啊！
SpongeBob,
are you down here?
海绵宝宝，
你在下面吗？
Yi!
呀！
- Hiya, Squidward.
- 你好，章鱼哥。
- Eeh!
Do not touch me!
- 呃！
不要碰我！
I am way out
of my comfort zone.
我已经出路了
我的舒适区。
All right, you've been
down here longer than me.
好吧，你已经
在这里比我还长。
Which way?
哪条路？
- Pull my finger.
- 拉我的手指。
That way.
那样。
- Figures.
- 数字。
- * Sewer, sewer, cha cha cha,
sewer, sewer, cha cha cha *
- *下水道，下水道，恰恰，
下水道、下水道、恰恰*
* Sewer, sewer,
cha cha cha *
* 下水道，下水道，
恰恰恰恰 *
Look at these strange etchings,
Squidward.
看看这些奇怪的蚀刻，
章鱼哥。
- Look like snakes.
- 看起来像蛇。
- I hope we don't run into
anything like that down here.
- 我希望我们不会遇到
这里有类似的东西。
Hey!
Over there!
嘿！
在那边！
It's stuck on the pipe!
卡在水管上了！
- We need to get
up there!
- 我们需要得到
上面！
[grunting]
Ow! Huh?
[咕噜声]
噢！啊？
- * Sewer, sewer,
cha cha cha *
- * 下水道，下水道，
恰恰恰恰 *
- There it is!
[grunts]
- 就是这样！
[咕哝]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- [grunts] Ah!
Darn it, I missed again.
- [咕哝]啊！
可恶，我又错过了。
[screams]
Leapin' lampreys!
[尖叫声]
跳跃的七鳃鳗！
They're biting me!
他们在咬我！
- Well, bite 'em back!
- 好吧，咬回去！
- [screaming]
My eyes!
- [尖叫]
我的眼睛！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
- Hey, look,
there's the safe!
- 嘿，看，
那里有保险箱！
- Where?
Where?
- 在哪里？
在哪里？
- There it is.
- 就在那里。
* O sole mio *
*我的太阳神*
- Silencio.
- 沉默。
- Yay!
Whoo-hoo!
- 耶！
呼呼！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
- What the--
[snake roars]
- 什么是--
[蛇吼]
both:
Sewer snake!
两者：
下水道蛇！
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
[marching band music]
[行进乐队音乐]
- It's five minutes
to halftime.
- 五分钟了
到中场休息。
Do you know
what that means?
你知道吗
这意味着什么？
- [chuckles]
Sure do,
- [轻笑]
当然可以，
the Bikini Bottom-ettes!
比基尼内裤！
- The halftime wave, man!
- 中场休息，伙计！
When every toilet
flushes at once!
每次上厕所的时候
立刻就红了！
The sewers
can't take it!
下水道
受不了！
It's madness!
这太疯狂了！
- Okay, but you're gonna miss
the cheerleaders!
- 好吧，但你会想念的
啦啦队们！
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
- In here!
- 在这里！
- Ooh, Look!
"You are here."
- 哦，看！
“你在这里。”
- Why is the diagram shaped
like a giant sewer snake
- 为什么图表是这样的形状
像一条巨大的下水道蛇
with the arrow pointing
to its stomach?
与箭头指向
到它的胃里？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
- Oh, crossing "Digested
by a giant sewer snake"
- 哦，穿越“消化了
被一条巨大的下水道蛇“
off of my to-do list.
从我的待办事项清单中删除。
- Oh, that makes sense.
- 哦，这是有道理的。
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Snake food!
[screaming]
蛇食！
[尖叫]
- Good going, Squidward.
You're tickling him.
- 干得好，章鱼哥。
你在挠他痒痒。
I'll help you!
我来帮助你！
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
Squidward, the safe!
Squidward? Safe!
章鱼哥，保险箱！
章鱼哥？安全的！
- [screaming] Don't bother me
while I'm hysterical!
- [尖叫]别打扰我
当我歇斯底里的时候！
Aah!
啊啊！
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Oh!
- [grunts]
- 哦！
- [咕哝]
- Oh.
- Ah!
- 哦。
- 啊！
I'm alive?
I'm alive!
我还活着吗？
我还活着！
- I guess
we're just lucky.
- 我猜
我们只是幸运。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Oh, look,
you found the safe.
- 哦，看，
你找到了保险箱。
- Just my luck.
- 只是我的运气。
[intense music]
[激烈的音乐]
[buzzer sounds, all cheering]
[蜂鸣器响起，全场欢呼]
- Got to go!
- Oh, boy!
- 得走了！
- 哦，孩子！
all:
Oh! Oh!
全部：
哦！哦！
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
Egads!
哎呀！
Too much flushing,
she's gonna blow!
冲水过多，
她要爆炸了！
[panting]
[alarm blaring]
[气喘吁吁]
[警报声]
How's she holding up?
她还坚持得怎么样？
- Sir, every tunnel is flooded
except for the reducer pipe.
- 先生，每条隧道都被淹没了
除异径管外。
- The pinch point!
- 关键点！
- Hmm.
Is that bad?
- 唔。
那很糟糕吗？
both:
Huh?
两者：
啊？
[both whimpering]
[两人都呜咽]
- Gaskets blown,
manifold mangled,
- 垫圈被吹坏，
歧管损坏，
backflow everywhere!
到处回流！
- Oh, you're overreacting.
-哦，你反应过度了。
- You flushed it all away,
Crupski!
- 你把一切都冲走了，
克鲁普斯基！
You two better hope
你们两个最好希望
that fail-safe
I installed works.
那个自动防故障装置
我安装了作品。
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Hot dogs, popcorn.
- 热狗，爆米花。
Snorkles?
通气管？
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Good thing today was
Free Ax Day at the stadium.
- 今天的好事是
体育场免费斧头日。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[growls]
[咆哮]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
[all gasp]
[全都喘气]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
This is what you get
when so-called fishkind,
这就是你得到的
当所谓的鱼种时，
in all its hubris and ignorance,
stoops so low
在其所有的傲慢和无知中，
弯得这么低
as to cut corners
in its plumbing system.
至于偷工减料
在其管道系统中。
Extinction is the result
of being cheap!
灭绝就是结果
便宜！
- What a bunch of malarkey.
- 真是一群胡言乱语。
- At least we didn't waken
the Great Sewer Snake.
- 至少我们没有醒来
下水道大蛇。
Check that.
检查一下。
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
[snake roars]
[蛇吼]
Ah!
啊!
[snake roars]
Ah!
[蛇吼]
啊！
- Uh-oh.
- 呃哦。
Whoa! Ooh! Whoo-hoo!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
哇！哦！呼呼！
哇！哇！哇！
[all gasp]
[全都喘气]
- Hey, everybody,
the cook's back from toilet.
- 嘿，大家，
厨师从厕所回来了。
- Who's hungry?
- 谁饿了？
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]